Contact

court.m.tucker@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/courtt3d (LinkedIn) courtt3d.blogspot.com (Portfolio) ctucker9233.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills HTML5 CSS JavaScript

Certifications
Build Website Uls

Honors-Awards
Graduated with Honors

Courtney Tucker

Web Developer

El Cajon, California

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer, leveraging a background in retail and web management to build user friendly experiences for all users. Received an education in Game Art and Design from the Art Institute of California San Diego. Actively learning new skills through UCSD Full Stack Development Bootcamp, including HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js,SQL, and MongoDB.

Experience

Cash and Carry Furniture 13 years 2 months

Information Systems Manager December 2018 - Present (1 year 3 months) Greater San Diego Area

As the information systems manager, I have rapidly learned the RetailVantage POS software. After initial training provided by the software company, I can teach and advise all the employees about how to properly utilize it. I have helped to implement changes in current operating procedures if needed and to provide quality assurance. I have successfully helped to improve the company's workflow.

Web Content Manager May 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months) Greater San Diego Area

I am solely responsible for managing and maintaining our e-commerce site. I use software such as Photoshop to quickly and efficiently create and maintain images for over 3,000 products.

Software/Programs/Languages Used:

- -BigCommerce
- -Photoshop
- -HTML/CSS/Javascript

Skills Utilized

- -Graphic Design
- -Attention to Detail
- -Coding/Scripting
- -Excellent Communication
- -Critical Thinking and Problem Solving

Office Assistant/Data Entry Specialist/Data Analyst January 2007 - Present (13 years 2 months)

Process customer invoices and manage the filing system.

Organize and sort merchandise invoices

Receive merchandise on dock, tag all items accurately and enter items in computer

Collect data from Point of Sales System and generate accurate Sales Reports
Review computer generated reports to ensure the accuracy of data
Develop a database system to track merchandise received and merchandise
paid

Sales Associate Trainee
July 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 7 months)

I'm currently training to become a sales associate in the retail furniture industry. I love helping customers find that perfect piece. It's like a treasure hunt. I look forward to learning the business and improving customer service.

Skills Used:

- -Customer Service
- -Multi-tasking
- -Communication
- -Problem Solving
- -Good listener
- -Fast learner

CT Video Editing (Client: Educate For Life)

5 years 6 months

Youtube Video Editor and Podcast Creator January 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Greater San Diego Area

I have created over 160 Youtube ready videos for my client, Educate For Life. I utilize the Screenflow software to sync up the production audio with the video and perform any other edits that my client wants. I create podcast audio that

accompanies the Youtube video and it gets posted on iTunes, TuneIn, and many other podcast platforms.

Powerpoint Presentation Re-designer and Video Editor September 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 5 months)

- *Unify the Layout and Design of Multiple Power Point Presentations
- *Prepare each presentation according to a style guide
- *Upload presentations to file share system for use in online video classes
- *Edit videos of presentation and presenter for use on Udemy.com
- -Sync audio with video
- -Edit video in Screenflow to fit time requirements
- -Export and Upload videos to online platform
- -Keep all files well organized

Glacier studios Environment and Prop Artist February 2014 - September 2014 (8 months)

Virtual

Involved in all aspects of creating 3D Prop and Environment Assets.

Racket Games

Artist

August 2013 - January 2014 (6 months)

Create concepts, mock-ups, and various art assets.

The Art Institute of California, A College of Argosy University Student

July 2010 - June 2013 (3 years)

Worked on various group and individual projects. Modeled, unwrapped, and textured game ready assets using 3DS Max, Maya, Zbrush, Photoshop, and UDK.

Sony Online Entertainment Internship - Environment Artist October 2012 - December 2012 (3 months)

Greater San Diego Area

Interned for the Clone Wars Adventures team where I created many assets that have been released in-game.

Education

The Art Institute of California-San Diego Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Game Art and Design · (2010 - 2013)

Additional Creative Education (2011 - 2011)

San Diego State University-California State University Computer Science · (2008 - 2010)

University of California San Diego Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, Web Development · (2019)